9/7/2018 sobin Ceev

Sobin Mathew CTO @Lepardtechlabs

sobinmathew988@gmail.com +919633845820 https://www.linkedin.com/in/sobin-mathew-b98b9a90/https://github.com/sobin007 Kottayam,Kanjirappally,Kerala

Profile

An experienced Full-stack developer who has a track record of success creating apps that are both well-received and commercially viable. Skilled with working as a team and incorporating input into projects. Ability to always look for ways to improve upon an already existing app to keep people downloading it and enjoying it. Strong eye for detail and tenacity to never quit on something until it is absolutely perfect.

Skills

Android

Nodejs

Vuejs

Aws

Education

Bachelor's Degree – Information Technology Kottayam,India

Mahatma Gandhi University 2012-2016

Experience

Chief Technical Officer (CTO) Leopard Tech Labs (P) Ltd

April 2017 - Present Kanjirappally,Kerala,India

Responsible for overall technology vision including product selection, service offering and Product Management. Administrator for Google Apps and Salesforce created and maintained custom Salesforce Integrated with third Party REST API's and developed backend administration applications Project manager for outsourced technologies.

Android Application Developer Rhydo Technologies (P) Ltd

October 2016 – January 2017 Cochin, Kerala, India

Part of a team that would plan to develop and create mobile applications to match the needs of industrial clients. Assisted in auditing complex applications and creating a report of suggested changes. Assisted in creating app progress reports for large industrial clients.

Projects

Need2Spot

2017-2018

A system developed to feature business and services in every district of Kerala. It is set to be Kerala's largest business directory. N2S will be a simple platform for users to access solutions for their many needs. Website:

https://www.need2spot.com

Play Store :

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=roncyex.ventures.android.need2 spot

Big4Mapper

A system developed to help map the 4 main poisonous species of snakes throughout India. The system was developed to aid the study of habitation patterns, population etc.

Website:

http://snakebiteinitiative.in/

Play Store :

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=leopard.tech.lab.big4mapper

RoadWatch

Roadwatch is a system developed for CSI of WTI in order to help them study the number of roadkills happening in India.

Website: http://roadwatchers.org/ Play Store:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=watch.tech.lab.RoadWatch

9/7/2018 sobin_Ceev